The radiance of the night shines through my window
but the path to immortality is long.
The Eight Views and Nine-Bend Streams are desolate.
Living beings question the miseries of the world over a jar of wine.
Forget about Nirvana and rebirth,
I will break through the waves with my own flesh and blood.
The heavens are vast, so what if I was born mediocre ?
I stare at the Dao in my moments of madness
as the storm rages just below.
I've been thinking about life and death in my dreams.
I've unsheathed my sword to ask the immortals
why the world is a-changing.
Heaven and earth reveals its poignant truths.
Swallow the Four Seas and the Eight Wastelands,
experience all the vicissitudes of life in an instant.
I will defy the light in the sky
to continue to write a new chapter for all things in the three realms of existence.
Just a thought separates mortal from immortal.
Transform your insignificant body into light.
The hardships of the journey
will temper this young man's heart.
If I become a Renegade Immortal, will I hesitate to fight the heavens ?
Renegade Immortal
Subtitles by Bonobosubs
https://discord.gg/Ceckd4pdVA
Enough.
Gu Yundun
Sky Demon Country's Demon Emperor
Rank 3 000 000 Demonic Energy
(Illusory Yin)
If you continue,
I'll throw you in the Dragon Pool to feed the Old Jiao.
You're playing favorites !
He's the one who bullied me first !
Demon Emperor Sword's
Sword Spirit
You were about to level my entire Sky Demon City...
Moreover, he left the Hong Prison with his own skill.
How does that count as bullying you ?
You...
are too spoiled.
I don't care.
This isn't over.
Where are you going !?
Let me out first !
This Demon General Competition
is getting more and more interesting...
Look,
your hair is all messy.
Let's go.
I want to go over there.
Let's go see the front.
Let's go, let's go.
I'm sure you'll like it.
Alright.
Wan'er...
This sorrowful melody is bone-chilling...
How fitting...
Cultivators who defy the heavens
are destined to be forever lonely...
Under the starlight and moonlight,
a solitary shadow sipping wine
listens to the zither, savoring life.
I don't know how the cultivators who cultivated
for tens of thousands of years endured this loneliness.
But I know
that if one doesn't have at least a tiny bit of emotion,
they are only cultivating their self-created Dao
and not the Dao of the heavens.
Heaven and earth are inhumane.
Cultivating is about defying the heavens,
but if a cultivator is heartless,
they are also inhumane.
Using an inhumane heart to cultivate the heaven's inhumane Dao...
How can that be called defying the heavens ?
What does "defying" even mean ?
That is merely following the will of the heavens.
Since ancient times, those who followed the will of the heavens
were favored by the heavens.
But in reality they were merely insects.
The heavens can only be defied
through emotions.
Cultivating to defy the heavens
doesn't mean seeking to be immortal,
but seeking to get rid of my status as an insect !
That is what it means to rebel !
Note: 逆 rebel / defy here is the same character used in the title Renegade Immortal.
Wan'er...
We will meet again.
This is my promise to you.
So he also is a heartbroken man...
Interesting...
Have you found him ?
I'm sorry for my incompetence...
Where could he have gone ?
It can't be...
Brother Wang !
Where have you been ?
I just went out for a stroll
to clear my mind.
Were you afraid I had left ?
Of course not !
I have important matters to discuss with you.
Attendant,
brew some tea for Brother Wang.
Right away.
Brother Wang, after your experience in the Hong Prison,
what's your strength level ?
Even without that palm strike,
I can defeat you.
Good.
Very good !
My efforts were worth it
if you've improved that much !
If you can truly help me win the Demon General Competition,
I will personally recommend you to the Demon Emperor
to secure a Demon General position for you.
There's one more thing.
Vice Commander-in-Chief Xuan has accumulated a lot of military merits over the years.
Now that Commander-in-Chief Xuan is dead,
he's sure to take that position.
Most importantly,
he's favored by the Demon Emperor.
If he can recommend us to the Demon Emperor,
our road ahead will be way easier.
Tomorrow,
I want to take you to visit him.
What do you think ?
I'll follow Brother Mo's plan.
There are many visitors at the residence today.
Xuan Residence
Sky Demon City
Master is already seeing someone.
General Mo, please follow me to the side courtyard
and wait for a while.
I wonder who Vice-Commander-in-chief Xuan is receiving.
Vice Commander-in-Chief Xuan
Rank 300 000 Demonic Energy
(Early stage Ascendant)
You're not the first to come here.
I'm aware
of your request.
However,
your mediocre gift
doesn't impress me !
General Mo's Great Rotating Disk
has already reached the 18th layer.
Not bad.
If Vice Commander-in-chief favors me,
once I'm appointed,
I'll do everything I can to help you.
We are all soldiers of the Sky Demon Country.
Our loyalty is to His Majesty.
However,
I will remember
what you said.
Thank you, Vice Commander-in-chief !
This aura...
feels familiar.
That was Mo Fei.
He was faster than us.
I pay respects to V...
You're not kneeling before me ?
You have some guts.
However, in this competition,
you have at most 40% chance of winning.
Adding this person,
I'm 90% confident !
Use your full strength.
Let me see what you're worth.
Forgive me.
What's your name ?
Wang Lin.
General Mo has gained a fine subordinate.
It's hard to predict
who will win the competition now...
We hope for Vice-Commander-in-chief's favor.
I, Mo Lihai, vow to repay you in the future.
In this competition,
you'll have to rely on your own strength.
You both...
are dismissed.
Understood.
This guy's strength is unfathomable...
This is an order:
from now on,
the residence is closed !
Demon General...
Rely on their own strength ?
Brother Wang,
I must tell you something.
There is a lot of scheming before the Demon General Competition.
Demon Generals are protected by imperial decree
but their helpers
often die mysteriously.
Mo Fei ?
The details of what happened today
have probably already reached his ears.
This man
is no stranger to stabbing in the back.
Before the competition,
I need to cultivate in seclusion.
You must be careful, Brother Wang.
Don't worry.
A spy reported that
Mo Lihai is in seclusion
and this man is alone outside.
That saves us the trouble of looking for him.
He didn't even set up a defensive restriction ?
He's not afraid of death at all.
Maybe...
he thinks no one will dare to attack him ?
Proceed as planned.
Since Master has requested it,
we must ensure
that he dies !
Ink-Tip Spear,
attack !
Primordial Heaven Seal,
fall !
His finger spell is powerful
but with the Primordial Heaven Seal suppressing him
and with the Ink-Tip Spear,
there's no way he can survive.
What the hell is this spell !?
How many people has this person killed ?!
Could he be cultivating the legendary Dao of slaughter ?
Since you've come here,
why are you already leaving ?
The competition hasn't even started
but blood has already been spilled.
Interesting...
The assassination failed
but this is far from over.
Main Hall
Sky Demon City
So your fighting spirit is high
and you wish to have a preemptive duel with Mo Lihai ?
This isn't a bad idea.
Granted.
Thank you, Your Majesty !
Your Majesty,
the Demon General Competition is an ancestral tradition.
If we allow these two to set a precedent for private duels,
I'm afraid in the future...
If in the future, someone can be like Mo Fei and earn millions of military merits
by killing in the Fire Demon Country.
Then I...
will grant it to them as well.
His Majesty has allowed my private duel with Mo Lihai.
You will deliver
this challenge letter.
The Demon General Competition
is none of my business.
But this Seventh Purple Disciple...
Stop right there !
This person's cultivation is not beneath mine.
His sword intent is astonishing.
General Mo Fei
challenges you to a duel
3 days from now
at the Ancient Pavilion.
We hope
that General Mo
will not avoid this duel.
He's here !
I heard the All-Seer is quite proud of this disciple.
If I kill him,
I'll be heavily rewarded.
Seventh Purple Disciple,
would you like to spar with me ?
How could my Da Lou Sword Qi shatter upon impact ?!
What kind of spell did he cultivate ?!
Wei Yang Sword Slash !
What a waste of a good sword.
Damn Beast !
You...
I have no grudge with the Da Lou Sword Sect.
Sect rivalries are for our elders to decide.
We don't have to be enemies
within the Demon Spirit Land.
This man is no joke,
letting him go is unwise !
He broke my sword intent
and my sword slash...
He's stronger than me...
He will definitely become a serious threat to our Da Lou Sword Sect !
This man...
must die !
I use my Soul Blood to awaken Master's Sword Qi !
Slash !
Wang... Lin...
Ling Tianhou's Sword Qi is very powerful.
If he had succeeded in using this Sword Qi,
even with my Life Seals,
I would've died for sure.
A cornered beast is hard to fight,
always give the enemy a way out.
Brother Wang, what excellent scheming !
So this is the life-saving Sword Qi
that Ling Tianhou gave to his 12 disciples before they entered.
It seems to obtain the Sword Qi,
I must first refine the Origin Soul.
3 days later
This Sword Qi's power is earth-shattering.
Wei Yang really gave me a great gift.
He's badly injured.
Mo Fei's Great Rotating Disk
even broke the Hundred Waves Demon Sea that His Majesty taught me.
I lost...
I made an agreement with Mo Fei before the duel.
The loser will not participate.
Now,
whether I can obtain the Vice Commander-in-chief position
entirely depends on Brother Wang !
I will accomplish
what I promised you.
I've been walking this path for endless years
just to catch a glimpse of your silhouette.
Is it the compass of fate
that wrote this outcome for us ?
The heavens want to erase your existence,
that's the obsession guiding me.
Is this the path to uncover
truths from falsehoods ?
In a world of murk and shadow,
only the flame of truth can light the way.
Look at them all,
being carried by the waves.
being drowned.
I don't want to believe in whoever decides fate,
I will let the world refine my soul.
So what if I become an Immortal and defy the heavens ?
I will fight.
I'll break through the abyss of despair
to finally learn who I really am.
My body is stained by the bloody color of slaughter,
I embrace this obsession.
I won't glance back at the wasteland I left behind.
Even if this suffering shatters my soul
and I'm reborn countless times in hell,
I'll still fight.
It's hard to avoid loneliness
when you are above everyone else.
Can a moth that has witnessed the flames of a Suzaku
be afraid of a firefly ?